"One, two, three, four, you accept!"
"I'll teach one by one, you learn it."
"If you tilt your head and see me, I get charmed."
"My heart burns in fire..."
"One, two, three, four, you accept!"
"I'll teach one by one, you learn it."
"One, two, three, four... One, two, three, four..."
"The legs dance tying the wheel to the leg."
"I search for myself by stepping aside."
"The rain sings by touching my forehead."
"It flows to the middle of my lips."
"Hay...hay hay hay..."
"All the clouds passing over the mountain..."
"Now it touches over your head and drizzles."
"Ae...ayya...ayya..."
"One, two, three, four, you accept!"
"I'll teach one by one, you learn it."
"A movie which both of us can watch in a single ticket..."
"Is that a color movie that you and I play?"
"Is it a magic or mystery, that you are doing?"
"You are killing me with your glances."
"I am going to change you as a cotton."
"Like a wind, I am going to take you higher..."
"One, two, three, four, I accept!"
"Teach me one by one, I'll learn."
"If you take support, I'll hold you in my chest."
"I'll take you in my lap."
"One, two, three, four, you accept!"
"I'll teach one by one, you learn it."